# Mostapha El Amine BENLAGHA

Full-stack Web Developer

I am a web developer with more than three years of experience and an array of knowledge in many different front end and back end languages, responsive frameworks, databases, and best code practices. My objective is simply to be the best web developer that I can be and to contribute to the technology industry all that I know and can do.

fm\_benlagha@esi.dz

0795836081



mostafaben.github.io



github.com/mostafaben

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Lead Front-end developer**

soBiapi

11/2021 - Present

Algiers

- Front-end development
- Team lead

## FullStack web developer

Inside 360 Algérie

09/2021 - 11/2021 Alaiers, Alaeria Image and Marketing Consulting Agency VR / AR / XR Specialist Google Certified 451 Bouchaoui 2, 16084 Algiers, Algeria.

- Developement Team Leader
- Front-end development
- Back-end development

## FullStack Web developer

**EURL ITEXC Agency** 

06/2019 - 04/2021

EURL ITEXC Agency, is computer science and IT solutions agency.

- Design UI/UX
- Front-end development
- Back-end development
- Trainer

#### FullStack Web developer

Freelance

01/2017 - Present

- Front-end development Angular | React | vanilla JS
- Back-end development Laravel | Node.js
- Design UI/UX

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Computer Science**

ESI-SBA - Ecole Superieure en Informatique

2015 - 2017

#### **Bachelor in Computer science**

University Of Science And Technology Houari Boumediene

2019 - 2020

## TECHNOLOGIES







Laravel

python

React Native

## **PROJECTS**

E-commerce Platform - BABASHOP (2019)

An e-commerce platform that allows online businesses

E-Learning Platform - The Brave Spirit (2020)

Learning Platform or course management system (CMS)

Realization of preventative site BRAVE SPIRIT (2020)

Representative site for an psychiatrist

Tourism Platform - SAFARIATCOM (2020)

platform that is suitable for both travelers, travel agencies, and all other players, an online platform that offers all the necessary services for the tourism sector in Algeria.

Workshop Management & Ecommerce Platform - Roukaia Shop (10/2020 - 02/2021)

server-based workshop management package, which includes all the features required for the end-to-end running of garage or workshop business. with Online Booking module allows for customers to check availability and book products online

E-commerce Website FullHousedz (2021)

simple e-commerce website that allows online businesses

## PERSONAL PROJECTS

Food Mobile Application (2017)

- This application is a **Native Android App** for Algerian food, which is mainly based on searching ingredients in order to meet the needs of users and also to spread the culture of Algerian food in the Arab world.

Covid-19 Mobile Application (2020)

React Native Application for digital contact tracing during the COVID - 19 pandemic, i.e. the process of identifying persons ("contacts") who may have been in contact with an infected individual

URL Shorter - React Application (2021)

React Free URL shortener to create perfect URLs for your business. it helps you create and share branded links with custom domains at scale

Books Platform Back-end (2021)

Node.js server for books platform so that readers can exchange books between each other

### CERTIFICATES

Responsive Web Design - freeCodeCamp (2021)

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures - freeCodeCamp (2021)

JavaScript - TestDome (2021)

Cisco networking and security fundamentals - ICT-Towers (10/2016)